We spend a lot of time trying to help them out there. We need to do the client education part. That's how it is. It's actually not really efficient that way and it will not help you to stop the problem.
So what I recommend is, I just want to give a quick point and tell you, we have a plan to do everything. So we understand you have a lot of questions and we will help you to stop it.
Because the Outer Maker, everyone comes to us, they use us a different way to ask the same question. But the Outer Maker is actually, we know our clients want to mitigate the risk.
They want to get a plan to do. They want to save the tax. They don't want to pay tax as a non-rested. And they want to pass the immigration.
Yeah, we all understand that. And you just need to let us have some time to review your things, do your work, do the work. And then we will get back to you with an answer.
And then by that time, we will have more chance to discuss about if you agree with a certain approach, if you have different perspective, we will definitely respect your decision.
And then we will like to know how to do it. But yeah, at this stage, I would recommend, let us do the analyze. Let us try to propose something. Let us tell you the timeline. Let us try to do everything.
Okay, because the reason you pay us is you trust our professional experience, right? Like we will do all this work. Yeah.
You know, I actually thank you for calling. I've been waiting for this call to be honest. You know, for you, I do trust you. Because we talk and James, my girl, who reference to you.
And I know you also working with other friends. His friend actually reference you. So I have the, you know, the trust in you. But it's just sometimes like Amanda, when she asks me questions, it makes me worry.
To be honest, it's, you know, I know you guys are professional. I know you guys are busy. I know you're busy. And that's why, you know, for me, you know, I, you know, I'm kind of guy.
I, you know, I, I grew up in a place where it's communist country, right? So I, I will take everything responsible myself. This is my best way of doing everything.
Do you see like I, I draft something or all this because I'm just afraid, I'm just afraid you guys are so busy. You guys miss, uh, understandings or, you know, you see me, uh, you know, I also like you.
I'm a, I, I rather, I rather, I, I know this actually, I know I paid for you at this premium price. I know you will do a good job.
But I'm just myself, it's just this way you work with me because I think if we work, for example, with this hand, we're going to work together in a long time because it's me.
I want to be in a long time relationship. I want to find someone like you. To be honest, I want to find someone like you because, yeah.
I think, I think, I think, I think it is, uh, I would say that, uh, usually it's a cultural thing. I don't know if you, uh, because it's, it's very different in Canada.
Like how we approach tech and how we approach business. Like, uh, the approach we are using and including communication from our team, uh, this approach we have been using for over 10 years.
Okay.
So, yeah, then the template, then the question, and then, uh, usually in 99 for nine of the specific days, if our client just, uh, responds to a request, we will give them a peace of mind.
We just need some time to inspire a lot of the questions that you ask, like, uh, it's like you, uh, there are some wording that, for example, if you use, ensure something, uh, you want to guarantee something for IRCC, your immigration application.
Okay. Um, to be really funny, like, no accountant or professional would, uh, then you'll respond in writing because those are completely outside our advisory, like, role.
Um, the thing is, like, uh, like, uh, like a CPA, like, we need, we will be responsible for, uh, comment and advice, um, just at the same time, uh, we want to, like, you know, like, like some of this, like, communication.
I believe it's just in the cultural difference, or, uh, you, you are a really detail-oriented person, which we appreciate, but at the same time, uh, we want to do the way in Canada that is efficient to solve the problem.
Yes, uh, I, I understand that you have a lot of affection, that's why I think this call is, you know, it's, it's necessary.
I, I know that, like, I need to give you a call and then try to explain the situation.
Um, just, like, I, I would say it again, like, relax, and then let us, uh, do the work, and then we will have the chance to discuss everything in details until the point that, oh, you feel, oh, you are confident, and then we will send the response.
Yeah, because, uh, now, like, a lot of questions, I just, I, I would say they are paraphrased in different ways, but they are just asking the same thing.
We, we actually kept the votes up and down in the call, um, that we discussed last week, and, um, it's okay, it's because, um, the knowledge part is different, right?
That's why you, you come to us.
Um, just, I, I would say that, um, in some particular that I would say that, uh, please understand that, like, uh, unfortunately, you, you have really limited time knowledge, and, uh, that's why it's the time to try to, um, understand, like, our perspective, and why we need to do this.
It's not because we want to just take time and not answer your question or whatever, because a lot of the time, like, for example, I, if you have a really good example, if, for example, you cause the RA, or, uh, you, you mentioned a whole bunch of others, like, oh, I'm not rested, and blah, and all that should be, like, completely removed from your mind, because this, like, uh, this is just over-analyzed,
and being really paranoid, and, and this will not help the case, yes, because, uh, our ultimate goal is, like, we, we have working with you to be friends, you, and work out your back interest, so, uh, we know what is the point.
Sometimes, uh, in your mind, you need to get rid of those very first guests.
Yeah, um, may I say something, yes, uh, so thank you for calling, um, and try to clarify it. I, I agree, I agree.
There's, um, you know, Gary, there's one thing, Gary, um, so when, if Amanda asked the question differently, it would, it wouldn't trigger me.
I just, you know, like, because I went after, I, I paid for you guys, I always did a lot of studies, okay, and I know you guys are one of the tough, and that's why I, I decided to go with you guys, with you specifically, to be honest, because I, I talk to you, so I trust you.
So, like, when Amanda asked me questions, where, the way she talk, you know, I'm, I'm a detail-oriented guy, come on, I'm a fucking founder, right?
I'm a founder, I, I have businesses, I'm, at this age, you know, I've been experiencing a lot of stuff, and, uh, it's not, it's, it's okay, all the things, I'm, I'm not sure, I'm sure that I have unlimited, I, I have limited, in all of the time, that's why I'm here with you, right?
Because you know all this, and I love to work with you.
I would say, don't, like, precipice too much emotion, in the email, it's just a standard procedure, when there's questions, or those questions, we, we ask the big questions to over, like, 500 to 1,000 clients.
So, uh, please don't take over, uh, analyze about those. Uh, I understand you may want to, uh, different phone, but, like, I don't know, like, in, in a professional setting, or outsmell, uh, they, uh, they are, they are, this template, like, inspect, do you think it's just certain things, you think it's not professional? That's my, that's my concern now, like,
I mean, I mean, I mean, if, if it's you, I, if it's come from you, like, if she, uh, it, in, like, telling me, like, hey, it's Gary telling me, okay, so we're gonna, because she, when she asks the questions, okay, so, they're gonna do like this, they're gonna keep the 60,000, right?
So, she asks my wife, okay, the one thing is, or ask me, okay, I was like, oh, come on, I, I need more assessment from, from Gary, because I don't know whether it's come from her, Amanda, or it's come from you.
So, you can ask for clarification, right, like, you don't need to, I think one of the common, like, thing that, uh, we need to be really upfront with our client is, we, uh, professional accounting, you know, when we have a lot of complaints, it goes under our perk.
So, like, our client should not just, uh, just rely on my work, but, like, what, the whole correspondence, the process is part of the service, okay?
So, when we send out something, we are responsible.
Yeah, totally.
So, when I send something to you, if you need clarification, you just need to respond, you can say no, can you explain certain things, why you make this gesture,
we are open to give you more explanation, however, if you just reply, oh, yes, you agree, but later on, uh, you actually disagree, that's not an effective communication, okay?
So, regardless what position the person is, uh, because I cannot do everything, like, I have, like, uh, over, like, we have hundreds of this type of case every year,
and then, uh,
So, that, that's also, that, that's one thing I worry too, that's one thing I worry.
Yeah.
Everyone just comes to me to confirm everything so detailed, so, I, I mean, uh, please don't take it, like, uh, personally or take it as an emotion.
So, if you want more details, if you want to clarify what I'm saying, then please just focus on that question and try to ask us to elaborate.
Um, and, and for now, like, uh, what we want, what we don't want is, like, our client, um, raising a lot of different new questions or just paraphrasing all the questions and ask for the same thing.
Um, the thing is, we understand, we understand how, how our clients want to achieve the goal, but we are, we are in the same, we are in the same goal, so, we just want to make sure you give us time to do our work.
Yeah.
I definitely will give you guys time to just, like, tell me when, or tell me, Amanda, like, hey, give us a few days, I will answer you this.
I mean, she responds really quick, really fast, I like it, but the one thing is, I, I don't feel, like, I don't feel, like, uh, like, sudden or I don't feel, like, uh, like, free of mind, you know what I mean?
Like, if it's you, you call, you talk, it just looks like, it's, yeah.
Let me straightforward, we never ever received this type of email from clients in the last 10, 15 years, or in Amanda's history.
Uh, maybe she is new, but even I never received this type of message, uh, like, telling us the timeline or the recap of post and post.
So, this is, uh, something that I, I just want to explicitly tell you that, uh, we will, we know the ways how to do things.
So, uh, we appreciate our client to, uh, just let us do our work, and then we will, we will give you an explanation of different things.
And, uh, because a lot of the questions is not something we can advise in writing, and if it's out of our screen, for example, if you mention IRC,
or the, uh, your PR application, um, those, it's not something, uh, we, we provide detail response to writing.
I, I can't discuss with you as a friend or as a, as a professional, um, uh, outside of school, but the thing is, it's not something we will answer in the email.
Oh, yeah, I mean, it just, it just tell me uniquely, because I thought, like, the one thing is, um, you know, I, I know, like you said, you actually do all this immigration stuff too,
like, the accountants CPA of immigration, so I, I thought, because I just want, I, I just want, I just want, I just want Amanda to, when I recap it, I know it, it takes a lot of time for me to think about all this, but I just want to make sure that, because I don't know whether it's from your team or just from,
I just want to make sure that you're not going to be able to do all this, but I just want to make sure that you're not going to be able to do all this, but I just want to make sure that you're not going to be able to do all this, but I just want to make sure that you're not going to be able to do all this, but I just want to make sure that you're not going to be able to do all this, but I just want to make sure that you're not going to be able to do all this, but I just want to make sure that you're not going to be able to do all this, but I just want to make sure that you're not going to be able to do all this, but I just want to make sure that you're not going to be able to do all this, but I just want to make sure that you're not going to be able to do all this, but I just want to make sure that you're not going to be able to be able to do all this
Okay, Gary, I'm, hey, we are a businessman, it's okay, you throw me things, and I, I listen, Gary, I just want to, you just tell Amanda that maybe it's just my style, and just when say something, or when do, do things, just telling me like, okay, this is actually, make sure that it's actually she assess this, and it's actually coming from your team, because I don't know like, because I only know you, I don't know her profile.
Okay, I'm lucky.
And we have three real procedures, and then, yes, and then, and then again, yeah, because our team, every day, like myself, I have over 1,000 emails, and Amanda has a couple of hundred for sure, so we are very responsible for our clients, but it's really pretty good.
Yeah, I think that's why, you know, like, hey, I, I think that's a great way that you call to communicate to me, because maybe I'm, I'm always a little different than a lot of people, it's just my way of doing business, and doing things.
Yes, but, yeah, I just wanted to introduce, I guess, a bit of a, in Canada, in Canada, we, we want to be multicultural, we, we want to be multicultural, we, we want to be multicultural, we, we
we, we
We, we