We have a quick time to review your things, do your work, do the work, and then we will get back to you with an answer.
By that time, we would have more time to discuss. If you agree with certain approach, if you have different perspective, we will tackle the issues like respect your definition, and then we will like to know how it works.
But yeah, at this stage, I would like to let us try to help you with the plan. Let us try to do everything.
Because the reason you pay us is because you trust our professional experience. We will do all this work.
I actually thank you for calling me. I have been waiting for this call for the artist. For you, I do trust you. Because we talk and James, my girl who is reference to you. I know you are also working with other friends.
I have the trust in you. But it just sometimes, like Amanda, when she asked me questions, it is making work. To be honest, I know you are a professional. I know you are busy. I know you are busy.
I am a character. I grow up in a place where it is a communist country. I will take everything responsible myself. This is my best way of doing everything.
You see, I drag something on all this. I am just a very, you guys are so busy. You can miss the understanding. You know, you see me. I also like you. I am a bowler. So, whatever I do, I do everything to account.
I know I pay for you at this premium price. I know you will do a good job. But I am just myself. This way you work with me. I think if we work together in a long time, because this means I want to be a long time relationship. I want to buy someone like you.
I think I would say that usually it is a cultural thing. I don't know if you have, because it is very different from how we approach tax and how we approach taxes.
I think that the approach we are using is in terms of the publicization of our view. This approach we have been using for 10 years. So, the publicization of our view is that the complex and the question and usually in 99 for 9% of the fees, if our clients respond well, we will give them a piece of money.
So, the thing is, when we were responsible for our comment and advice, just that the thing is, we wanted some of this complexation.
I believe it is just a cultural thing. If you have a really detailed answer first, I would appreciate that. I have a thing for you. I will be working on it in a way that is efficient.
I understand that you have a lot of attention. That is why I think this point is not very eye. I know that I need to keep your voice and try to understand the situation.
I would say that, like we like to let that be the word, and we will have different security and heat. I am sure that you will point out all your feelings and then we will then respond.
Now, I will say that the apparent things in different ways, but they are just asking the same things. We will be actually comfortable to sound in the call sound.
It is okay if the knowledge part is different, right? That is why you come to us.
I would say that the particular of all fans, that are actually understand that. Unfortunately, you have to really be with the past knowledge. That is why I have been trying to understand our perspective and why we need to do this.
It is not because we want to just stay in time and not answer your question or answer. Because a lot of times, like for example, if you are really good example, for example, you can hold your voice or you are not restable.
So, that should be completely different from your mind. Because this shows over analyze and being really paranoid and this will not help a case.
Yes, because of how often they go as like, we have worked here with you to be friends.
So, we know what it is for some time. If you mind, it could definitely not go very far.
Yes, but I say something. Thank you for calling. I agree. There is one thing to do.
So, when Amanda asked the question differently, it would trigger me. I just, you know, like, because I went after I came to you guys, I always did a lot of studies together.
And I know you guys are one of the top. That is why I decided to go with you guys and review specifically to be honest, because I talked to you as well.
So, like, when Amanda asked me questions where the way she talked, you know, I am a detail all together. Come on, I am a fucking father. I am a father. I have businesses. I am at this age, you know, I mean, it is beyond a lot of stuff.
And it is not, it is okay, all this thing. I am not sure. I am sure that I have limited knowledge intact. That is why I am here with you. Because you know all this. And I learned to work with you.
And they don't feel like I have reached 50 much emotion. And the email is just a separate approach. The general one has questions or questions. We react to things, questions, you know, for like 500 to 1000 clients.
So, please go take over annualize about those. And as you may want to different home, like I don't know, like in professional fasting or out to them. They are just pamphlet. Like, do you think it is just certain thing? You think it is not professional? That is my concern now, like.
I mean, if it is you, I just come from you, like telling me, hey, it is Gary telling me, okay, so we are going to, because when she asks the questions, okay, so they are going to do like this, they are going to keep the 60,000s, right? So she asks my wife, okay, the one thing is, or ask me, okay, I was like, oh, come on, I need more assessment from Gary.
Because I don't know whether it is come from her, Amanda, all is come from you.
You can ask for care and patience, right? Like, like that, you don't need it. I think one of the problems, like things that we need to be really important about finding this, we are professional and kind of need to know that we have that we love the complaints, it is both under our current soul.
Our plan should not just rely on the hindrance of the whole correspondence, of course, as part of the service, okay. So when we take a soul-dain, we are responsible.
So, if you need care and patience, you just need to respond, you can say no, then you explain certain things, why you make this special.
We are all trying to give you more explanation. However, if you just rely on, yes, you agree, but later on, you actually disagree, that's not an effective communication.
Okay, so regardless what position we are in, because I cannot do everything, like I can have over, like, only a country of this problem, based every year.
And that's also, that's what I think I worry to. That's what I think I worry.
So, I think everyone just comes to me to confirm everything about the health. So, I mean, please don't take it personally or take it as an emotion.
If you want to be told if you want to care for what's happening, then we just focus on that question and try to help us to do the absurge.
And for now, what we want, what we don't want is our client releasing a lot of different new questions or just paraphrasing all the questions and answers that ask for the same thing.
The thing is, we understand how our client wants to achieve the goals. But we are in the same goals, we just want to make sure you keep us fine to do our work.
No, I definitely will give you guys time to just tell me when or tell me, my man that I like, hey, give us two days, I will answer you this.
I mean, she responds really quick, really fast. I like it. But the one thing is, I don't feel like certain or I don't feel like free of mind.
If it's you, you call me talk. It's just like, yeah.
For the world, we never ever be gifted with help of each other. I have seen the last 10 years or even in the entries. Maybe she is new, but even I never be gifted with message.
Like telling us the timeline or the recap of both and both. So this is something that I just want to explicitly tell you that.
We know the way how to do things. So I appreciate how I am here. Just let us do our work. And we will give you an explanation of different things.
And because a lot of the question is not something we can advise in writing. And if it's out of our, for example, if you mentioned IRC, or your application,
so it's not something we, for IP tell is also writing. I can't just get here as a friend or as a professional outside of school. But the thing is not something that you are answering.
No, I mean, it just, it just tell me, you know, because I thought like the one thing is, you know, I, I know like you said, you actually do all this immigration stuff to the cow 10 CPA expectations.
I just want to make sure that because I don't know it's from your team.
I just say that, like, what's on the word you, you put into the app or like something that you create a, or this, I would say that I live in a dress or you sell and also, but so I'm not that good to hear you because we do have a lot of other cases.
It's okay. It's okay. It's okay. We are businessmen. It's okay to control me things. And I listen. I just want to, you just tell Amanda, maybe just my style, just when say something, or when do a new thing, just telling me like, okay, this is actually, make sure that this is actually she assess this.
And that's actually coming from your team because I don't know like, because I only know you. I don't know her profile.
So, like, you know, we are responsible for her.
I'm glad to hear.
And we will, I'll be happy with real close features. And then again, yeah, because I'm on team every day, like myself, I have also a profile for email and Amanda, I have a profile for my future.
So, we are very, very active. But, in a really big size, if you want a bit more to come from things, just do think that, yeah, we have people, yeah, I have a way of thinking.
Yeah, I mean, that's why, you know, like, hey, I think that's the way that you call communication. Because maybe I'm always a little different than all people.
Yeah, yeah.
I just wanted to say that I get the information kind of, you know, in Canada, we will be able to be multicultural, be an effective group of communication styles.
But when we handle this kind of sensitive, direct method, we need our clients to follow all of this.
Yeah, I definitely, but just tell them that the one thing, I also have a lot of clients, I work with clients.
So, different clients, they have a different way of communication, not everyone's the same.
So, for sure, you are working together, for sure, you know, like the way you call me like this, you're not trimming me like every client.
So, you call me telling me this and you're actually taking to consideration that I have a little bit of concern that you call, which is a great way for you to do business.
That's exactly what I'm going to do, too.
It's just like, sometimes, I would do, because Amanda, if she just say things in a way that it's just, you know, it's not emotional, but for me, it's just for me.
Oh, she don't know that. Is that just for me?
I would say that if this is, if it's just a distraction, right?
Like, a lot of the time, I realized that our clients just give too much information where we ask, like, we want to be examined, like, you should do that.
And actually, only about information, the 10, maybe basically, I mean, two filter hours, like, one of the information I would talk about, like, a printer, which is not helpful when we are really busy.
I also want to, like, emphasize one point that is, like, usually in similar cases, for clients like Nestle, who only gives them, like, their feminist call, like, because you're prepared by them, like, we actually give you a lot of interest, but, you understand, you have a lot of professional users, but I think you'll be able to, for, not certain more,
not certain more, not about that. But your concerts, like, I understand, you're out to people, so your concerts, you think you can think of that too much for Merrill?
Gary, if you said so, I would love to. I hate, I, you know, if you said so. I mean, I just want to know, like, okay, Gary and the team already can see the whole information.
That's why I just want Amanda to say. And if that's the case, then I'm fine.
So, I'm saying is like, because you said that right now, I'm saying, you know, I already take everything to consideration. So, I just, because Amanda, when she answered, I asked me questions, I'm scared, because I don't know whether it's from your team or from you or it's just from her, because I don't know how you know.
Yeah, you just over analyzed.
Yeah.
So, like in a lot of our cases, like our, especially for, you know, in reverse fire, they have no clue what the, uh, talking sometimes, they, uh, they have no clue what the group is.
They would tell us information that is incorrect.
And they would tell us, like information is consistently, and they would tell us the information is by you.
So, um,
like, you know,
you know,